Alexei Brilevski

FRONT-END DEVELOPER





+375 29 617-20-37



brilevski.alex@gmail.com



Minsk, Belarus









SKILLS

- · React, Redux, Redux Toolkit
- JavaScript/ES6+, TypeScript
- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- · REST API, Axios, Redux-Thunk
- · React-Router-Dom, Formik
- TDD, Jest
- StoryBook
- Material UI
- · Git, GitHub

EDUCATION

IT-Incubator

Front-end developer (React/Redux/JS/TS)

2021 - 2022

Belarusian State University

Manager-economist

2005 - 2010

LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate (in progress) Belarussian, Russian - Native

ABOUT ME

Qualified and professional front-end developer with experience in creating SPA using React (JS/TS), Redux, HTML and CSS.

Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. Planning to study Node.js, because in future I see myself as a Full-stack developer.

My free time is dedicated to Codewars, programming tutorials and boosting my English.

Ready to consider a project work and full-time employment in a creative company with up-to-date tasks and collaborative team. Open to your suggestions.

EXPERIENCE

My Portfolio

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, PART-TIME PROJECTS

Study Cards (Start-up project)

May 2022 - July 2022

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios. Formik. Team development.

GitHub link

Social Network (Self-education project) Mar. 2022 - May 2022

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom,

Axios, Redux-Form, Reselect, TDD.

GitHub link

To-Do List (Educational project)

Feb. 2022 - Mar. 2022

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, Formik, TDD, Material UI, Storybook.

GitHub link

MARKETING SPECIALIST

2010 - Present

- Contextual advertising setup (Google Ads, Yandex Direct).
- Statistics analysis and campaigns support.
- Website audit, analytics system setup.
- · Procurement of goods. Shipping control, reporting.
- Communication with suppliers and clients.